BELLO ADETAYO OLAMIJI

Software Developer/ Web Developer

Phone: 08139680568

Email: belloadetayo@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/bello-adetayo-olamiji-

436375221/

I'm a Frontend developer experienced in building websites for small and medium-sized businesses. Hardworking, willing to learn more, delivering of jobs on time. Knows HTML and CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, Nest.js, Node.js, WordPress, Bootstrap. Full project management from start to finish. Regular communication is important to me.

RELEVANT SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

REACT.JS

NEXT.JS

REACT NATIVE

NODE.JS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CashToken Reward Africa, Lagos NG

December 2022-Present Internship Training/ Software Engineer/Frontend

- Building of client side of the website
- Designing and proper Structuring of the website
- Building a responsive website.

Paul Osaji & Co

May 2017-August 2018

Field Officer

Taking measurement of landed properties and collections of data.

Ademakinwa & Co

March 2017–May 2017

Office Assistant

- Typing of Real Estate properties related letter and Book keeping.
- Outsourcing of properties

Lagos State Polytechnic (LASPOTECH), Lagos State HND: Estate Management & Valuation	August 2022
Lagos State Polytechnic (LASPOTECH), Lagos State OND: Estate Management & Valuation	August 2018
TRAININGS	
Available on request	
REFRENCE	
Available on request	

EDUCATION